https://www.jrosenberg.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Law Offices of John Rosenberg A Professional Law CorporationPrivacy Policy | Law Offices of John Rosenberg A Professional Law Corporation
Call Now For A Personalized Consultation (818) 530-1770HomeAbout AttorneyPractice AreasPersonal InjuryMotor Vehicle Accidents (Truck, Motorcycle, Bicycle)Slip and FallConstruction InjuriesBurn InjuriesElectrocutionSpinal InjuriesDog BitesProduct LiabilityPedestrian InjuriesAmputationsHead Injuries and ConcussionFracturesView AllTestimonialsResultsFAQsFree InformationArticlesVideosGeneral VideosAuto Accidents VideosDog Attacks VideosSlip and Fall VideosPersonal Injury VideosFree DownloadBlogsContact UsMenu HomeAbout AttorneyPractice AreasPersonal InjuryMotor Vehicle Accidents (Truck, Motorcycle, Bicycle)Slip and FallConstruction InjuriesBurn InjuriesElectrocutionSpinal InjuriesDog BitesProduct LiabilityPedestrian InjuriesAmputationsHead Injuries and ConcussionFracturesView AllTestimonialsResultsFAQsFree InformationArticlesVideosGeneral VideosAuto Accidents VideosDog Attacks VideosSlip and Fall VideosPersonal Injury VideosFree DownloadBlogsContact Us Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Get Help NowHome » Privacy PolicyHomeTerms Of UsePrivacy PolicyContact UsLegal MarketingCopyright©2020, Law Offices of John Rosenberg A Professional Law Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
The 5 Worst Mistakes That Can Ruin Your Injury Claim
× Download Attorney John Rosenberg free book and get meaningful information about your personal injury claim and lawyer selection.
Your Name *
Email *
Phone *
Close Download Guide Now
